Contact

+92 341-2768730 (Mobile) abdullahwaqas08@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/abdullah-waqas-939944114 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

HTML5

CSS3

Javascript

Languages

Urdu

English

Publications

CI/CD with React
Unit test and CI with Angular2
React native collapsible
React simple editor

Abdullah Waqas

Senior Software Engineer at 10Pearls Karāchi

Summary

Young energetic and experienced Frontend Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Javascript, Selenium WebDriver, ReactJs, Angular2, NodeJs, Unit testing framework. Strong engineering professional graduated from Karachi University.

Experience

10Pearls

4 years 3 months

Senior Software Engineer
January 2020 - Present (2 years 1 month)

Software Developer November 2017 - December 2019 (2 years 2 months)

TallyMarks Consulting
Front-End Developer

June 2017 - November 2017 (6 months)

Responsibilities include the translation mockups to actual code of websites and

web apps, implement ajax web services on front-end provided by the back-end team.

Kiddom

3 years 10 months

Front-End Engineer

January 2016 - July 2017 (1 year 7 months)

Responsibilities include the translation mockups to actual code of websites and

web apps, implement ajax webservices on front-end provided by back-end team, also write UI web automated tests using python+selenium as well.

Front-End Engineer

October 2013 - December 2015 (2 years 3 months)

Education

Karachi University

Computer Science · (2011 - 2015)

DJ Sindh Govt Science College Intermediate, Pre-Engineering · (2010 - 2011)

Dars Gah Khursheed Secondary School Matriculation, Science · (1997 - 2009)